https://www.hoganleather.com/privacy-policy/

What information we collect online
In several areas of our site, we ask you to provide information by filling out and submitting online forms. These areas include:
Contact form
Wholesale Request form
Order checkout form
In these areas we may ask for your name, address, email address, credit card and other information needed to complete your order or fulfill your request.
In order to make improvements to our site, we may use this information to help show us how customers use the site.
What information we do not collect
We do not gather sensitive personal data (e.g. health, genetic, biometric data; racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, sexual orientation, and criminal convictions). We expressly request that you do not provide any such sensitive data to us. Additionally, our services are not directed to children under 13. If you learn that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without consent, please contact us.
How we use the information we collect
We have a strong tradition of providing excellent customer service. Our goal is to bring this tradition to the online environment by providing a listing of our products and services.
The information we gather when you visit our site may be used in aggregate to improve the products and services we offer you. In the end, we hope this information will help us tailor our communications so that you receive more of what you want from us and less of what you don’t. This is a means of receiving feedback from our customers, and we encourage you to email us with your questions or comments. We read every email we receive.
Please note that we do not sell or share email addresses with other companies.
What information we do not share with others
We do not share, sell or trade email addresses, information collected as part of a survey or specific details about you or your household. We do not contribute to or participate in shared or cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your personal information. We do not release credit card or financial information for use by other companies. For privacy purposes, all information relating to our customers is stored on a highly secure server.
Controlling Your Information
If you are an EU resident, you have certain rights concerning the information we hold about you, as defined under the General Data Protection Regulation. If you wish to exercise these rights, please contact us, including your email address in the first instance (this is the unique identifier we use to identify and collate personal information).
Requesting: You may request a copy of any data we hold about you. Upon request, we will provide a relevant digital file containing the personal data we hold on record about you.
Correcting: The accuracy of your information is important to us. If you change email address, or if any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please contact us so we may correct our records.
Deleting: You have the right to request erasure of your personal information. Unless there is a compelling reason for the data not to be erased (for example, if we need to use that data to fulfil our contractual or legal obligations), your personal data will be deleted on request.
Use of Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Our website uses the following cookies:
Google Analytics: Google Analytics sets cookies to help us accurately estimate the number of visitors to the website and what content is most popular. This helps to ensure that our website is responding to your needs in the best way possible. Please note that your IP Address is anonymized prior to being sent to Google Analytics.
YouTube: Any videos embedded on our website rely on third party cookies from YouTube to function. As these cookies are set by YouTube, we have no direct control over their usage.
Facebook: Our site may use Facebook Like buttons, embedded Facebook feeds, or other embedded Facebook features that rely on third party cookies from Facebook to function. As these cookies are set by Facebook, we have no direct control over their usage.
By using and browsing our website, you consent to cookies being used in accordance with this Policy. If you do not consent, you must turn off cookies or refrain from using the site. Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. To do this, look at the ‘help’ menu on your browser. Switching off cookies should not noticeably restrict your use of this website.
Cart
Accessibility
Contact Us
Mailing List
My Account
Customer Service
FAQs
Privacy
